kepware.com 2019-04-27

# Privacy Policy | PTC

﻿

_LAST UPDATED 22-January, 2019_

Privacy Policy.pdf?la=en&hash=BE086CDB8019A13EB89292FB0BB0FE54)

### Contents

  1. Scope
  2. PTC Apps
  3. Information we may Collect from or About You
  4. Where we Store and access your Personal Data
  5. How we Use Information About You
  6. Job Applicants
  7. Transfer and Disclosure of information About You
  8. You can Opt-Out of E-Mail Correspondence and Access and Correct the Information we collect
  9. Data Integrity
  10. Security
  11. Limitation on Scope of Privacy Principles
  12. Compliance and Enforcement
  13. Unlawful Use of PTC Software
  14. We do not Knowingly Collect Information from Children who are Under 13 (or under 16 in the EU)
  15. Other Sites
  16. Your rights
  17. Data retention
  18. Changes to our Privacy Policy
  19. How to Contact Us
  20. PTC Subsidiaries

  1. ### Scope

**PTC Inc.** and its subsidiaries and affiliates (listed here)  ("We" or “PTC”) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This Privacy Policy ("Policy") explains the basis on which we process any personal data we collect from or about you, or that you or any third party provide to us, not only from the use of our websites, such as  [www.ptc.com](http://www.ptc.com/) and www.kepware.com (or any site that is linked to this Policy) (our “Sites”), but also in connection with managing our workforce, conducting our business, through our software products, apps and services including SaaS and cloud services, and from any other means.  Please read the following carefully to understand our practices regarding how we process personal data and how we will treat it. 

We may revise this Policy from time to time. The most current version of this Policy will govern our use of your personal data. If we decide to change our Policy, we will post the updated Policy on this site and update the Policy modification date. Please check back regularly to review any changes to this Policy. 

"Personal data" means any information or set of information that relates to an identifiable individual, either directly or indirectly.  Personal data does not include information that is encoded or anonymized.

  2. ### PTC Apps

For information about how personal data is processed by certain PTC Apps, please refer to the app specific websites:

  3. ### Information we may Collect from or About You

_Personal Data_

We may collect and process the following data about you:

    * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our internal or external sites, including our Sites, and information you provide on independent partner sites that is transferred to us. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our sites, subscribing to our services (for example PTCUniversity or IOTU.com or support services), downloading free and trial versions of our software, posting material or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our sites, our software and services or reporting suspected piracy.
    * If access to our services is created by or at the request of an organization (an “Organization”) of which you are an employee, contractor, member, agent or other participant (each such user referred to as an “Organization User”) your "Organization’s Administrator" may provide us with certain personal data, such as your name, email address, and telephone number and organization name.
    * If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.
    * We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them.
    * Details of transactions you carry out and of the fulfilment of your orders, including the downloading and licensing of software.
    * Details of your visits to our sites including, but not limited to, traffic data, data regarding the site pages you visit, weblogs, and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise, and the resources that you access.
    * Information that you supply to us in the course of general marketing and other business activities.
    * Information that you supply to us when you visit our facilities or while attending an event (either in person or online) at which PTC is a host, a participant or which is sponsored (in whole or in part) by PTC such as Liveworx. We may also make video recordings and take photographs at live events.
    * Information that you provide or disclose on notice boards, newsgroups, community feedback sites, email systems, forum facilities, chat rooms, or similar features that we may establish on our sites. 
    * Device-specific information collected by PTC’s software Performance Advisor functionality described below and other tools embedded within our software products. All personal data in such tools is anonymized by default – PTC has no legal way of reversing this process.
    * Information that is provided to PTC by third parties such as our business partners, in the course of PTC providing and supporting PTC’s products and services.
    * Information that you supply to us or that we obtain/create in the course of your application for employment or engagement (for example, _salary, performance evaluations, benefits data, background checks_ ). See paragraph 6 below for more information about how we collect and process personal data from job applicants.

_IP addresses and other Technical Information_

When you visit any of our sites, we may collect information about your computer, including where available, your IP address, domain name, operating system and browser type, certain hardware or device information and other technical information. This is information about browsing actions and patterns and the use of certain software products and apps, and does not identify any individual except where user settings are configured by the user to provide personal data or where we have expressly notified you in the course of registering for, or accessing a service that personal data will be collected.

_Website Cookies & Beacons_

Our sites use cookies (a small piece of information that is placed on your computer when you visit certain websites) to distinguish you from other users, to track your browsing pattern and to build a profile of how you and other users use our sites. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse any of our sites and also allows us to improve our sites. If you have an online account with us, PTC also uses cookies to recognize you to pre-fill forms to save you time.  PTC does not mandate Cookies for you to access our sites, and you may freely set your browser to reject all Cookies or prompt you to accept or reject them.  Some of the cookies we use are session cookies and only last until you close your browser, others are persistent cookies which are stored on your computer for longer.  We may collect information through web beacons about your web browsing activities such as the address of the page you are visiting, the address of the referrer page you had previously visited, the time you are viewing the page, your browsing environment and your display settings.  We do this in order to optimize your browsing experience, the use of web-based services and provide you with relevant information on PTC products and interest based advertising. Please be aware that if you choose to block cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use those features, and preferences that are dependent on cookies may be lost. If you choose to delete cookies, settings and preferences controlled by those cookies, including advertising preferences, will be deleted and may need to be recreated. 

_PTC Performance Advisor_

In order to understand how our software is used, how it performs, and the preferences of the users, PTC utilizes Performance Advisor (also known as Quality Agent or Diagnostic Tool) to collect data on the use and performance of the Software. We will share this data with our business partners, for technical and marketing purposes.  The data collected is listed on the Legal Policies section on [www.ptc.com](http://www.ptc.com/) .

By default, Performance Advisor does not collect personal data, all such data is anonymized and PTC has not ability to access the personal data. You, or your Organization Administrator, may opt-in for the collection of personal data in which case PTC will be processing all personal data as processor on your behalf or on behalf of the Organization. 

_Free & Trial Versions of Software or Functionality_

If you are using a free or trial version or our software products or services or accessing certain free functionality within our products, we will use the personal data provided when setting up an account (which is required to download or access the functionality) to contact you about your experience with the products and to keep you informed about other products and services that we feel you may be interested in. You can opt-out of receiving marketing information, however you can not opt-out of the collection of the anonymized systems information though Performance Advisor. If you don’t want this system information to be collected, please don’t download or use the free or trial software or access the free functionality.

  4. ### Where we Store and access your Personal Data

PTC is a global company and as such personal data may be accessed anywhere in the world. If you are visiting any of our sites or communicating electronically with us, various communications will necessarily result in a transfer of information across international boundaries.  Accordingly, by visiting any of our sites and/or communicating electronically with us (including the in the process of our providing information, software or services to you), you acknowledge that your personal data may be processed in a country other than the one in which you reside. The transfer of personal data between PTC’s Affiliates is governed by a Global Data Transfer Agreement based on the EU Standard Model Clauses.  

  5. ### How we Use Information About You

In general, we will only process personal data where the processing is in our legitimate business interests or required to perform a contract with you or our corporate client. We use personal data held about you in the following ways:

    * To ensure that content from our sites is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer. 
    * To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you. 
    * To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.
    * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so.
    * In order to better service you with respect to PTC products and services that are available from time to time.
    * To notify you about changes to our service, updates to our sites, new PTC product offerings or special events hosted or sponsored by PTC or its business partners.
    * In order to enforce or apply our terms of use of any one of our sites, our software licenses, hosted services, and other agreements. 
    * To protect the rights, property, or safety of PTC, our customers, or others. To provide you with updates on any events you are registered to attend or interested in.
    * If you attend or speak at any of our events or events that we attend as a sponsor, we may make video recordings of such events for use in promotional and educational material.
    * If you visit our offices or sites, we maintain CCTV footage for the safety and protection of PTC and PTC’s premises.

If you are an applicant for a job or for engagement by PTC, we use personal data about you to determine your suitability for employment, job assignments and responsibilities in accordance with paragraph 6.

If you are an employee, we use personal data about you for various employment-related purposes, primarily relating to establishing and managing our employment relationship with you.  Please refer to our Employee Privacy Notice that is available on The Hub.

We may provide information to you in the form of emails, mailings, website displays or other correspondence methods.

We are interested in your views, and we value feedback, and we may therefore set up notice boards, newsgroups, community feedback sites, email systems, forum facilities and/or chat rooms on our sites. Any information that you disclose via such facilities will be used in accordance with the terms of service for the particular forum and in the absence of such terms of service, this Policy. However, we can of course not control and be responsible for other parties' use of the personal data which you make available to them through such facilities and otherwise on our sites. We encourage you to be careful about what personal data you share in this way.

PTC will offer individuals the opportunity to choose (opt-out) whether they receive communications from PTC or its authorized resellers concerning PTC products and services (as described further below). 

We will only use and share personal data in ways that are relevant for the purposes for which the information was collected or subsequently authorized by you. 

  6. ### Job Applicants

In sending us your Resume or CV, you are allowing us to store it with your contact details in our job applicant database. We will only share your personal details with the PTC HR team members, talent acquisition, third-party facilitators and consultants engaged to support the recruitment process, and PTC Interview Panel Members for positions that you have applied for or that may be of interest to you for a profile like yours. We may need to share your personal data with external third parties such as to local labour authorities, courts and tribunals, regulatory bodies and/or law enforcement agencies for the purpose of complying with applicable laws and regulations, or in response to legal process.  We will not keep your personal information in our candidate database for more than 6 months after the end of your hiring process (that is to say after the last call, interview, meeting or email that we have had / exchanged with you during the interview process), unless either we are required to keep such information longer by law or we have written agreement via email from you. We might ask final candidates for a reference check (we will always ask you first before contacting anyone for personal references) and for certain positions where we feel a background check is required, we might share your personal details (Email ID) with a service third party provider who will support this.

  7. ### Transfer and Disclosure of information About You

To Other Third Parties.  We may transfer or disclose personal data to other third parties who agree to process such personal data in accordance with our instructions and provide appropriate technical and organizational security measures. Such third parties may include:

    * Other members of the PTC group of companies where it is necessary for the efficient provision of services and the most productive use of PTC’s resources 
    * ·our authorized resellers and business partners for the limited purposes of offering our products and associated services.
    * To trusted businesses or persons to process it for us, solely on our behalf. 
    * In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.
    * If any PTC entity, or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.
    * If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our [terms of use of any](http://www.ptc.com/common/terms.htm) of our sites and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of PTC, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
    * government agencies or other third parties as authorized by applicable law: (i) to comply with legal, regulatory, or reporting requirements (such as reporting to tax authorities and employment regulators), (ii) in the event we are required to respond to a court order, subpoena, discovery request, or other legal process, or if, in our good faith opinion, such disclosure is required by law, (iii) at the request of governmental authorities conducting an audit or investigation, (iv) to verify or enforce compliance with applicable employee policies, laws, rules, or regulations, (v) in connection with corporate restructurings or potential acquisitions, mergers, or sales, or (vi) whenever we believe disclosure is necessary to limit the legal liability, or to protect or enforce the rights, interests, or safety, of you, the Company, our subsidiaries and affiliates, other employees, or third parties.

It is PTC's policy to never sell your information to list brokers or similar entities for commercial gain.

  8. ### You can Opt-Out of E-Mail Correspondence and Access and Correct the Information we collect.

In certain circumstances you may have the right to ask us not to process your personal data (“opt-out”).  We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) how we intend to use your data or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for the purpose for which it was collected.  If you want to opt-out please contact as set out below. 

You may also opt-out of future marketing correspondence by updating your preferences using the link on the footer of e-mail correspondence.

Upon request, we will provide you with reasonable access to personal data about you in our possession, and will take reasonable steps to permit you to correct, amend, or delete personal data that you demonstrate to be inaccurate or incomplete.  If you have a ptc.com online account, you may access the data that ptc.com has recorded and update or correct the information at any time.  You may also opt-out of future correspondence by updating your preferences.  To do this go to [www.ptc.com](http://www.ptc.com/) and under Customer Resources visit [ptc.com accounts](http://www.ptc.com/common/account/index.htm).  If you don’t have an account or are unable to locate your account information, you can create one or you may request a copy of the personal data we have stored and/or exercise your opt-out right by contacting dataprivacy@ptc.com.  When updating personal data about you, we may ask you to verify your identity before we can act on your request.  

We may reject requests that are fraudulent, unreasonably repetitious, require disproportionate technical effort (for example, developing a new system or fundamentally changing an existing practice), or would be extremely impractical (for example, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes). 

Where we can provide information access and correction, we will do so at no cost to you, except where it would require a disproportionate effort.  We aim to protect information from accidental or malicious alteration or destruction.  Accordingly, after your information is deleted, we may not immediately delete residual copies from our active servers or remove information from our backup systems. 

  9. ### Data Integrity

We will take reasonable steps to ensure that personal data that we process is reliable for its intended use, accurate, complete, and current.  You are responsible for the accuracy of all personal data you provide to us.  We will use reasonable efforts to maintain the accuracy and integrity of the personal data we obtain, and to update it as appropriate.  We will take reasonable steps to ensure that personal data is reliable for its intended use. 

  10. ### Security

We have implemented, and will maintain current, reasonable physical, technical, and organizational security measures for the purpose of protecting the personal data in our possession from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. 

Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our sites, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone. 

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we have security measures in place to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our sites; any transmission is at your own risk. 

  11. ### Limitation on Scope of Privacy Principles

Adherence by PTC to this privacy policy may be limited to the extent required to meet a legal, governmental, national security, or public interest obligation.

  12. ### Compliance and Enforcement

PTC Inc. will conduct periodic internal compliance audits of our relevant privacy practices to verify adherence to this privacy policy.   We encourage individuals covered by this Policy to raise any concerns they have about the way we process their personal data by contacting us at the address below.  

PTC Inc. commits to resolve questions and complaints about your privacy and its collection or processing of your personal data.   Individuals who believe that PTC or any of its affiliates is not complying with the terms of this Policy, can contact PTC’s Global Data Privacy Officer, 121 Seaport Blvd, Boston, Massachusetts 02210, or by email at [dataprivacy@ptc.com](mailto:dataprivacy@ptc.com), or though PTC’s “open door” enquiry and reporting platform at ptc.com/opendoor. We will answer any questions and to investigate any concerns or complaints. We will do our best to internally resolve any complaints and disputes regarding the use and disclosure of personal data brought to our attention.

  13. ### Unlawful Use of PTC Software

PTC regards software piracy as the crime it is, and we view offenders accordingly.  We do not tolerate the unlawful use of PTC software products, and we pursue those who do so using all legal means available, including public and private surveillance resources.  As part of these efforts, PTC utilizes data monitoring and scouring technologies to obtain and transmit data on unauthorized use of software. Such data may be transferred and processed in a country other than the one where the software is being used or accessed.  If you are using an unauthorised or unlicensed copy of our software, cease using it immediately and contact PTC to obtain a legally licensed copy. By using an unauthorized or unlicensed copy of PTC software, you should be aware that PTC will collect, use, and transfer personal data internationally for the purposes of identifying users of such software. This personal data may include online identification, such as IP address, MAC address and geolocation.

  14. ### We do not Knowingly Collect Information from Children who are Under 13 (or under 16 in the EU)

Our sites are not directed to children younger than age thirteen (13) or under the age of sixteen 16 in the EU.  We do not knowingly collect personal data from children under these ages on any of our sites and we will delete any such information later determined to be from such young person, unless we have received consent to collect such personal data from the child’s parent or guardian.  In the event a parent or guardian believes that his/her child has provided information to PTC and wishes that data to be removed or corrected, please contact PTC as described below.

  15. ### Other Sites

Our sites may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our authorized resellers, business partners, industry forums, analysts and to other sites that are relevant to our products and services.  Additionally, for some of the functions within our websites we link to/use third party suppliers for example, when you visit a page with videos embedded from or links to YouTube or slide-share.  If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies.  Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites. 

  16. ### Your rights

In certain circumstances, if you are an EEA resident, you may exercise the rights available to you under applicable data protection laws as follows:

    * If you wish to access, correct, update or request deletion of your personal data, you can do so at any time by contacting us using the contact details below.
    * In addition, you can object to processing of your personal data, ask us to restrict processing of your personal data or request portability of your personal data. Again, you can exercise these rights by contacting us using the contact details provided below.
    * If we have collected and process your personal data with your consent, then you can withdraw your consent at any time.This may mean your access to certain services is restricted or denied as a result. Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect processing of your personal data conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.
    * You have the right to complain to a data protection authority about our collection and use of your personal data.For more information, please contact your local data protection authority. 

We respond to all requests we receive from individuals wishing to exercise their data protection rights in accordance with applicable data protection laws.

  17. ### Data retention

Personal data will be stored in accordance with applicable laws and kept as long as needed to carry out the purposes described in this privacy policy or as otherwise required by applicable law. 

  18. ### Changes to our Privacy Policy

This Policy may be amended from time to time.  Any changes we may make to our privacy Policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail.  When amendments are made, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of this Policy.

  19. ### How to Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about our use of your personal information or this Privacy Policy, please contact us using the following details:

The Global Data Privacy Officer  
PTC Inc.  
121 Seaport Blvd  
Boston Massachusetts 02210  
Attn: Compliance Department – Privacy  
or  
or  
Version Update: January 22, 2019:  

Revision to address for The Global Data Privacy Officer only.

* * *

### PTC Subsidiaries:

_EEA Countries (including EMEA rep offices)_

**Country**

| 

**PTC entity**

| 

**Address and Registration No.**  
  
---|---|---  
  
Austria

| 

Parametric Technology Gesellschaft m.b.H.

| 

Operngasse 17-21, 1040 Wien, Austria

(Co No: FN 111171m Salzburg)  
  
Belgium

| 

Parametric Technology Belgium B.V.B.A.

| 

Esplanade Heysel 1, PB 94, 1020 Brussels 

Belgium 

(Co No: No 584607)  
  
Denmark

| 

Parametric Technology Denmark A/S

| 

Lynbyvej 14, st. th., 2100 Kobenhavn Ø 

Denmark

(Co No: CVR – NR – 16993433)  
  
Dubai

| 

PTC SSI Designated Activity Company – Dubai Branch Rep Office

| 

25/28 North Wall Quay, Dublin D01 H104, Ireland 

(Co No: 368456)  
  
France

| 

Parametric Technology S.A

| 

Immeuble L’Emeraude, 1 rue du Petit Clarmart

78941 Vélizy Villacoublay Cedex, France

(Co No: RCS AIX 380 280 081)  
  
Germany

| 

Parametric Technology G.m.b.H.

| 

Edisonstrasse 8, 85716 Unterschleissheim

Munich, Germany

(Co No: HR B 93462)  
  
Ireland

| 

PTC (SSI) Designated Activity Company

| 

25/28 North Wall Quay, Dublin D01 H104, Ireland

(Co No: 368456)  
  
Israel

| 

Parametric Technology Israel Ltd

| 

Nahum Hat 5 St, Tirat Carmel

PO B15019, Matam, Haita 31905, Israel

Co No: 51-162522-0  
  
Italy

| 

Parametric Technology Italia S.r.l.

| 

Centro Direzionale Colleoni, 

Palazzo Sirio 3, Via le Colleoni 11

20041 Agrate Brianza, Italy

(Co No: 1304782)  
  
Netherlands

| 

Parametric Technology Nederland B.V.

| 

Bèta Technology & Business Accelerator

Unit K110, High Tech Campus 9

5656 AT Eindhoven, The Netherlands

(Co No: 16070133)  
  
Romania

| 

PTC Eastern Europe S.R.L

| 

319G Splaiul Independentei Street, 14th Floor, Sector 6, Bucharest, Romania

(Co No: J40/7478/2008 )  
  
Russia

| 

PTC International Limited Liability Company

| 

Rusakovaskaya Street 13, 107140, Moscow 

Russia

(Co No: 1097760001569)  
  
Serbia

| 

Plugin76 R&D d.o.o. Subotica

| 

Boze Šarčevića 19, 24000 Subotica, Serbia

(Co no 21217743)  
  
Spain

| 

Parametric Technology Espana S.A.

| 

Gran Via de les Corts Catalanes

130-136, Planta 7ª, Barcelona, Spain 08038

(Co No: CIF A-60000593)  
  
Sweden

| 

PTC Sweden AB

| 

PT Sweden AB

Johan På Gårdas gata 5A, 41250 Gothenburg

Sweden

(Co No: 556450-3711)  
  
Switzerland

| 

Parametric Technology (Schweiz) AG

| 

Badenerstrasse 15, 8004 Zurich

Switzerland

(Co No: CH-020.3.003.036-9)  
  
Turkey

| 

PTC (SSI) Designated Activity Company Istanbul Liaison Office

| 

25/28 North Wall Quay, Dublin D01 H104, Ireland  
  
UK

| 

Parametric Technology (UK) Ltd

| 

Parametric Technology (UK) Ltd

Abbey House, 282 Farnborough Road, Farnborough, Hampshire, GU14 7NA

(Co no 2513030)  
  
_Non-EEA Countries_

**Country**

| 

**PTC entity**

| 

**Address and Registration No.**  
  
---|---|---  
  
Australia

| 

Parametric Technology Australia Pty. Limited

| 

AMP Centre, Level 34, Sydney NSW, Australia 1000

(Co no 071 284 761)  
  
Brazil

| 

Parametric Technology Brazil Ltda.

| 

Rua Samuel Morse, 120 – 3rd Floor, Sao Paulo, Brazil, 04576-060

(Co no) 35.214.131.377)  
  
China

| 

Parametric Technology (Shanghai) Software Co. Ltd

| 

Unit 008, Floor 8, 888 Wanhangdu Road, Jingan Distriict, Shanghai, China

(Co no:   
  
Canada

| 

PTC (Canada) Inc.

| 

3333 Cote Vertu, Suite 620, St Laurent, Quebec, H4R 2N1, Canada

(Co no 296722-7)  
  
Mexico

| 

Parametric Technology Mexico, S.A. de C.V.

| 

WeWorx, Paseo de la Reforma, Floor 42, Mexico City, Mexico, CP 06600

(Co no  
  
Hong Kong

| 

Parametric Technology (Hong Kong) Ltd.

| 

Unit 40, Level 3, three Pacific Place, Central, Hong Kong

(Co no 360181)  
  
India

| 

Parametric Technology (India) Private Ltd.

| 

Level 06, Nitesh Timesquare, M.G Road, Bangalore – 560001, Karnataka, India (Co no 55-60773)  
  
Japan

| 

PTC Japan K.K.

| 

8-1 Nishi-Shinjuku 6-chome, Shinjuku-ku, Tokyo, Japan  
  
Korea

| 

Parametric Korea Co., Ltd

| 

(Samseong-dong) 17 Floor, 521, Teheran-ro, Gangnam-gu, Seoul, Korea 06164

(Co no 89944)  
  
Singapore

| 

Parametric Technology Singapore Pte. Ltd.

| 

Unit 28-31, Level 42, Singapore 049909, Singapore

(Co no: 199202432C)  
  
Taiwan

| 

Parametric Technology (Taiwan) Ltd

| 

15/F Hsin Kee Building, 460-466 Hsin Yi road, Sec. 4 Taipei, R.O.C. Taiwan 110 Taiwan  
  
* * *
